她对自己和他人的安全都已造成威胁
She may be a threat to herself or others.
我们建议将她送至精神病院
We recommend that she be conveyed to the psychopathic ward
直到她神志恢复清醒
until her senses can be restored.
又来了一个 12条
Got another code 12.
名字?
Name?
Collins Christine Collins. Christine.
不 不 不 听着 这一定是弄错了
No, no, no, listen, this is a mistake.
证明警官?
Certifying officer?
J J  Jones队长 林肯岗分部
Captain J.J. Jones, Lincoln Heights Division.
不 不 求求你! 求求你! 警察们想要惩戒我
No, no, please! Please! The police are trying to punish me...
如果你一直这样 我就给你穿紧身衣
If you keep it up, I'm gonna have to put you in a straitjacket.
你想要那样么?
Do you want that?
不 女士
No, ma'am.
那你就规矩些 12条
Then behave yourself. Code 12.
我没疯!
WOMAN: I'm not mad!